Something interesting happened to
me with this show, which was, I
had a kind of quite comfortable way of
doing this show that I put together,
which
involved showing a whole
bunch of different books and
talking about each book, which it was
kind of devolving into a
PowerPoint presentation.
And I did some kind of early
versions of the show in
London at a kind of a Fringe theatre,
and I held all the books in a
suitcase. And I left them somewhere
on the London Underground.
The London Underground
features quite heavily in this.
And the London Underground, the
subconscious are probably
quite closely related
anyway. But anyway, some part of
me decided that that wasn't the way
to do this show and left those
books on the Victoria line, I think.
So kind of like, were they destroyed
in the controlled explosion?
I don't know.